Hi there,
first of all, I will, first of all today,
I will make a backend for, uh, uh, for my,
uh, for my Roka web project
where I will make APIs for it.
Uh, uh, where I will make APIs for my,
uh, WhatsApp bot project,
Roka WhatsApp bot project. I will make a login,
sign up, and,
uh, sorry, I will make a login API.
Then I will make a conversation,
errors, tunnels, leads, .py,
then I will connect, uh,
any 10 webhooks, then I will also set up the,
uh, then I will also set up the Roka,
Superbase, You Through Credentials,
where I will make tables for, I will also connect the Superbase
and integrate it, and I will make tables like Users,
Contacts, Conversations, Error Logs,
and Messages, these are the tables.
I will make, then I, then,
this is, uhm, the login page for Eroka Web Project,
then I will make a JWT authentication in that,
then I sign in, and log in, then I sign
in, and log
in,